{
    "subject": "resource/NetSuite",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "NetSuite Inc. is an American software company based in San Mateo, California, that sells a group of software services used to manage a business's operations and customer relations. Customers access these services over the internet paying a periodic subscription fee. NetSuite's services are primarily aimed at medium- to enterprise-sized businesses.",
    "human_readable": "NetSuite is an American software company based in San Mateo, California that sells a group of software services used to manage a business' operations and customer relations, which customers access over the internet paying a periodic subscription fee, with services primarily aimed at medium- to enterprise-sized businesses.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8842584490776062,
            "question": "What do NetSuite's software services primarily manage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8463757634162903,
            "question": "What type of businesses are NetSuite's services primarily aimed at?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8308643102645874,
            "question": "What is the main purpose of NetSuite's software services?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8291440010070801,
            "question": "What type of company is NetSuite?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.819673478603363,
            "question": "How do customers access NetSuite's services?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7968448400497437,
            "question": "What state is NetSuite based in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7293094992637634,
            "question": "What is the typical business size that utilizes NetSuite?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6313163042068481,
            "question": "Where is NetSuite headquartered?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5843468308448792,
            "question": "Is NetSuite a physical or digital company?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44607043266296387,
            "question": "What payment model does NetSuite use?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=NetSuite is an American software company based in San Mateo, California that sells a group of software services used to manage a business' operations and customer relations, which customers access over the internet paying a periodic subscription fee, with services primarily aimed at medium- to enterprise-sized businesses.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4479_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is NetSuite a physical or digital company?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4479_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is NetSuite headquartered?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4479_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the typical business size that utilizes NetSuite?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4479_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4479_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4479_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4479_138.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4479_145.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4479_150.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4479_168.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4479_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4479_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4479_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4479_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe statement provided in the query is supported by the context information. The documents state that NetSuite is a business technology vendor based in San Mateo, California, and provides applications for various business functions such as ERP, CRM, financial management, and project management, which customers access over the internet (cloud-based) through a subscription fee model, primarily aimed at medium- to enterprise-sized businesses."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided context information supports the statement that NetSuite is an American software company based in San Mateo, California. It also indicates that NetSuite sells cloud-based business management applications and services primarily aimed at medium- to enterprise-sized businesses. The documents describe NetSuite\u2019s suite of applications covering ERP, CRM, e-commerce, and other business functions, which are accessed over the internet with a subscription model."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}